KEVIN SALINAS

PROFILE

Name

Kevin Salinas

Address

3001 84th Street 1st Floor East Elmhurst, NY, 11370

Phone

646 812 4992

Email

KevinGSP@gmail.com

Websites

Kevingsalinas.me Linkedin.com/in/kevingsp

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY AT ALBANY

Albany, New York | 2014 - Present GPA: 3.40; Major: Computer Informatics Association for Computer Machinery Club

CITY COLLEGE OF NEW YORK

New York, New York | 2012 - 2014 GPA: 3.10; Major: Computer Science

PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

It is my goal to provide exceptional customer service and give clients a one-of-a-kind experience that is both personal and insightful. I have learned to intertwine both technology and customer service, which has led me to give outstanding help desk and IT work. I strive to learn how to create a User Interface and User Experience that is modern, streamline, and functional. Knowing what a customer wants and expects will help me achieve that.

EXPERIENCE

Apple Guilderland, NY 2015 - Present

Family Room Specialist/Tech Support

Take care of reservations and appointments daily. Troubleshoot multiple phones or other products. Provide exceptional customer

service and a great customer experience.

Capital District YMCA Clifton Park, NY 2014 - 2015

Member Service Representative

Perform front desk duties such as: answer phone calls, check members in, register for programs and take payments.

University at Albany, EOP Albany, NY 2014 - 2015

Computer Lab Supervisor

Manage the computer lab and make sure students are using their resources properly. Logged how the printer was used and also help fix any technical issues, whether it was hardware or software.

AVillage.., Inc. Albany, NY 2014 - 2015

Community Event Organizer/Designer Intern

Created and prepared presentations for the community in Downtown Albany. It showcased programs that our organization offers to help underprivileged kids progress.

YMCA of Greater New York

Long Island City, NY

2012 - 2015 Member Service Administrator

> Set up online program classes to register families and kids. Fix monthly billing for memberships as well as follow ups for prospective members. Take payments from 3rd party organizations and companies to create revenue to meet monthly budgets.

SKILLS

PROFESSIO	NAL	PERSONAL	
IT		Time Keeping	
Networking		Team Work	
HTML/5	1	Communication	_
CSS	•	Leadership	
MongoDB		Spanish	
MySQL		Multitasking	
Access		Independent	
JavaScript		Commitment	